istudies.com 2010-11-23

# iStudies.com - Privacy Policy

ISTUDIES.COM Privacy Policy

We at ISTUDIES.COM and our affiliated companies worldwide are devoted to respecting your online privacy and understand your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites.

ISTUDIES.COM has created the following Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand and appreciate the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of ISTUDIES.COM regarding information that we collect on our network of web sites and through our other Internet advertising mediums, including but not limited to email, newsletters, and leave-behinds. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ISTUDIES.COM do not own or control, or to people that ISTUDIES.COM does not employ.

Information Collected by ISTUDIES.COM  
Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information  
ISTUDIES.COM collects various sorts of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with more appropriate user experience. Some of this information is gathered automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the ISTUDIES.COM site, the pages of the site you went to and the URL of the page you went to upon leaving the site.

ISTUDIES.COM may also contract with honest & reputable third-party advertising companies to supply ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other procedures to collect your non-personally identifiable information.

Personally Identifiable Consumer Information  
In addition, at some of the ISTUDIES.COM web sites, we gather information that you may choose to provide to us when requesting additional information from us or from one or more of our clients. Examples of personally particular data that you may provide to us include name, address, and email address. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later choose to have your information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below.

How Collected Information is Used The non-personally identifiable information that ISTUDIES.COM collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other contents in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform the best and which content is most fitting for different individuals.

If you elect to provide ISTUDIES.COM with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from ISTUDIES.COM and from our clients. In addition, that information may be put together with information accumulated from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other ISTUDIES.COM sales and marketing efforts.

Sharing Information with Third Parties  
All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by ISTUDIES.COM. There are instances, however, in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of ISTUDIES.COM on an anonymous basis. When you request information from ISTUDIES.COM or one or more of our clients, we may transfer that information within ISTUDIES.COM or provide your information to our client(s), across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may present the information on their product or service that you requested.

We may also disclose information to a third party who provides considerably similar services as the original service about which you requested more information. In such situations, we will offer you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that ISTUDIES.COM is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business.

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that ISTUDIES.COM, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the happening of that such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information.

Finally, ISTUDIES.COM may share your information as necessary to act in accordance with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

Security  
Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within ISTUDIES.COM or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while ISTUDIES.COM will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure.

Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out  
Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting ISTUDIES.COM web sites.

Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Opting-Out  
You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to ISTUDIES.COM. If you choose to provide such information to ISTUDIES.COM, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, surveys or promotional communications via email, you may opt-out by clicking here and following the instructions to unsubscribe. To have your personal information completely removed from our databases, simply contact us at [Dennisb@perfspotmail.com](mailto:Dennisb@perfspotmail.com) and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Once we receive your instruction, we will take corrective actions right away.

Access/Accuracy  
To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, ISTUDIES.COM wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting ISTUDIES.COM should you need to update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to [Dennisb@perfspotmail.com](mailto:Dennisb@perfspotmail.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in the information that we hold as soon as practicable.

Children's Privacy In agreement with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), ISTUDIES.COM.com is not planned to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

Refer a Friend  
Some of ISTUDIES.COM's web sites offer you the opportunity to easily inform a friend of the offer or information promoted on the site. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a ISTUDIES.COM site, we will ask you for your friend's personally identifiable information, including name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. ISTUDIES.COM stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [Dennisb@perfspotmail.com](mailto:Dennisb@perfspotmail.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. Our one-time email to your friend will inform him or her of this fact.

Commitment  
Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and ISTUDIES.COM's web sites are constantly changing to meet these demands.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at Dennisb@iStudies.com  
. While we cannot guarantee privacy precision, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention.

Your Consent  
By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to ISTUDIES.COM's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy.

Contacting Us  
For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding ISTUDIES.COM's Privacy Policy, you may email us at [Dennisb@perfspotmail.com](mailto:Dennisb@perfspotmail.com) or forward your correspondence to the following address:

ISTUDIES.COM  
ATTN: Dennis Bryan   
4800 N. Scottsdale Rd.   
Suite 4500  
Scottsdale, AZ 85251

Phone: 888-311-7373 x 5874  
Email:Dennisb@iStudies.com
